Hello friends, welcome to
Technical Movie YouTube Hindi channel.
In today's video, people will learn
how to insure two wheeler third party in 2023 from ICICI Lombot. So I will
tell you the complete process. So, first of all, what you have to do is
search CSC in your Google Chrome browser and
go to the digital portal. As soon as you
click on Digital Seva Connect, you will be logged in
to the digital Seva portal.
After logging in, you will
see step by step like you have to
click on
[music]
and here you have to type on the insurance option.
As you type insurance,
then go down and
click on Motor Third Party.
As soon as you click on Motor Third Party, you will
search ICICI.
As soon as you click on click, you will be
redirected to the ICICI page.
From here, you have to scroll down
and I am showing you by highlighting it from
here
and from here you will click on First Party Third Party.
Do not say two wheeler in one step otherwise everyone may face problems. As soon as
you reach this page,
check here once that your page is on
desktop site.  Modify it so that you do
not face any problem. After that, what
you have to do here is simply that the bike
registration,
customer's registration date, everything will be
automatically added here. If it is not added, then
you can do it manually as well. So, let
me show you how much it is costing by entering a number. Like,
now if you click on the registration number, then
enter your bike number here.
Let me enter my bike number. As soon as you enter the
bike number, we click on Get RTO Details.
Nothing needs to be changed. Nothing needs to be
changed here. CC has not
come automatically, so you can select CC now.
We have selected our CC. As soon as we click on it, we will click on
Get Quote,
processing and you will see
784. If you do
not add your personal cover in it, if you add personal cover, then
that amount will also be added here. So, right now
we have to
generate the policy at the lowest price. In this, there is a
demand from 784 customers that we do
not want personal cover, so we have removed the personal cover from here.
If you want to take personal cover, then
you will not have to click on No here.
We do not want personal information,
we have CSC wallets, 784 only,
we will deduct it, after that we will click on proceed, in this
you will see a new feature,
complete KYC, so is it
necessary to do KYC or not,
you will also get to see all these things in this video, we are
watching here, you
can check once again, your details will be there,
after that chassis number engine number will
automatically appear, nothing needs to be done
here, if you want to give
KYC details then you can also give KYC details,
click on this, let me click on this and
show you what comes in the pop up,
if you fill the KYC details once, then
automatically whenever you
create an insurance customer,
all the details will be automatically filled here,
so it is very important to do his KYC, so
let us do KYC here now, we will
fill all the details here manually,
after that we will proceed, here
fill all the details of the customer like address etc. correctly, after that
click on get propose,
as here now enter the pin code
So the complete details will be shown to you there, so
whatever
address is shown in it according to the pin code, city,
state etc., you should fill it correctly, the pin
code which is on your RC paper, enter the same pin code
here, enter the name as per the RC
because unless your name
matches the RCM, your document will
not be considered valid, so whatever name
is on your RC, the
address on the RC should be the same as on your insurance
paper as well, so let us enter our pin code, if you find the
customer's mobile number or customer
care
number here then enter it, if not then there
is no problem, but if you want, you
can also enter your email ID here because the
policy is also sent to him on email, so if you can get the
email ID of most of the customers, then
provide the email ID of the customer only
so that he keeps getting emails and
notifications from time to time for policy
renewal, so let us enter our email and
mobile number of the customer, after that
click on Prostate,
after filling the simple details, you have to simply
click on Get Generate Proposal, like
Generate  Click on propose, the process will happen,
wait a little and here the entire
premium will be shown, like it is showing 784, only that much will be
deducted from your wallet and here
also we want to see the details again,
click on view and edit, then all the
details will be shown here, if you want to add some money in gas,
nominee etc. then you can add it from here,
if you do not want to add it then there is no
problem at all, from here you simply have to
click on nine, as soon as you click, it will be
direct to your CSC
and by asking your father for password and wallet the
policy will be generated
and you can give it to the customer, the policy is done by printing the policy, there is
no problem, there is
no special need for stamp etc., so
you can net the policies from here and
you can give the policy to the customer for at least only ₹784,
in 2023 in this way you
can insure all third parties,
you are not going to have any problems, so
how did you like this video, if any
information or any point is missing then
please comment on that also, you will
find the video  Let's go, see you in the next video, till then
bye bye, thank you.